<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Anne Boleyn</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>R.L.~Weston</author>
      <author>Bert~Lee</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
In the Tower of London, large as life,
The ghost of Anne Boleyn walks, they declare.
For Anne Boleyn was once King Henry's wife,
Until he had the axe man bob her hair.
Oh, yes, he did it long, long years ago,
And she comes back at night to tell him so.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
With her head tucked underneath her arm,
She walks the bloody Tower,
With her head tucked underneath her arm,
At the midnight hour.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
She comes to haunt King Henry, she means giving him what-for
Gadzooks, she's going to tell him off, for spilling of her gore.
And just in case the axe man wants to give her encore,
She has her head tucked underneath her arm.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Now sometimes old King Henry gives a spread,
For all his pals and gals, a ghastly crew,
The axe man carves the joint and cuts the bread,
When in comes Anne Boleyn to spoil the mood.
She holds her head up with a wild war whoop,
And Henry cries, &quot;don't drop it in the soup!&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
She walks the endless corridors, for miles and miles she goes,
She often catches cold, poor dear, it's drafty when it blows,
And it's awfully, awfully awkward for the queen to blow her nose,
With her head tucked underneath her arm.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
The sentries think that it's a football that she carries in,
And when they've had a few they shout, &quot;Is Army going to win?&quot;
They think that it's Red Grange instead of poor old Anne Boleyn
With her head tucked underneath her arm.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
One night she caught King Henry, he was in the canteen bar,
He said, &quot;Are you Jane Seymour, Anne Boleyn, or Catherine Parr?
Now how the heck am I supposed to know just who you are?
With your head tucked underneath your arm?
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
