<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Bastard King of England </title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 c2</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
Now the minstrels sing of an English king of many long years ago
He ruled his land with an iron hand though his morals were weak and low
His only other garment was a dirty yeller shirt
With which he tried to hide his hide but he couldn't hide the dirt.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
He was dirty and lousy and full of fleas
But he had his women by twos and threes
God bless the Bastard King of England.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
Now the Queen of Spain was an amorous Jane
A lascivious wench was she
She longed to play in her loving way with the king across the sea
So she sent a royal message with a royal messenger
To invite the King of England down to spend the night with her.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Well when Phillip of France he heard it by chance
He declared before his court,
&quot;The Queen prefers my rival just because I'm somewhat short.&quot;
So he sent the Count of Zippity-Zap
To give to the Queen a dose of clap
To pass it on to the Bastard King of England.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
When the King of England heard the news
He cursed the Gallic farce
He up and swore by the royal whore he'd have the Frenchman's arse
He offered half the royal purse and a piece of Queen Hortense
To any British subject who'd undo the King of France.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
So the Earl of Sussex jumped on his horse and straightway rode to France
Where he made a pass and he stripped the sash from Phillip's pajama pants
And in front of a throng he slipped on a thong
Leaped on his horse and galloped along
Draggin' the Frenchman back to merry England.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
When the King of England he saw the sight he felt in a faint on the floor
For during the ride his rival's hide was stretched a yard or more
And all the maids of England came down to London town
And shouted 'round the battlements, &quot;To hell with the British crown.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c2">
      <lines>
So Phillip of France usurped the throne
His scepter was the royal bone
With which he bitched the Bastard King of England.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
