<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Bianca's Lament</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Bianca</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 c1 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
He stood on a battlefield in a tabard of green
White stag leaping high on his breast
Two gold cups on his shield
And a field of blue o'er the rest
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
He called to his comrades "We fight for the King"
"For our Queen we lay down our lives,"
"For our ladies' honour we take up our swords"
"Outlands! Hark to our cry!"
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
Forward my warriors, Hark to the horn;
we go forth to fight and to die.
Be still sweet lady, 'tis not time to mourn;
for the white stag, he yet marches high!
Forward my spearmen, I stand with the shield.
Forward my swordsmen, I call.
To this angry horde, we never shall yield;
though to the last man, this day we may fall.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
I looked o'er the battlefield searching long for sword
And cups of my kinsmen and lord
Out numbered on the green, the White Stag and his men
Marched to meet the great foeman horde
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
My lord and my kinsmen stand ready to fight
Waiting only the call of the King.
LAY ON! Was the call and Outlands the cry
And sword on armour did ring
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
I stand on a battlefield piled high with the dead
With a cup for the warriors who live.
Though blessed cool water I bear to these men
And to them sweet succor I give,
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
My heart bleeds within me, for my lord lies just there
Run through for to save his king.
Long will I remember the battle this day
Long of its great heroes I'll sing.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
