<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Born on the List Field</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 c2 v3 c3 v4 c4 v5 c5 v6 c6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <comment>Originally written by the late Ivar Battleskald, he asked that it not be written down and instead passed through oral tradition. He lifted the ban before he passed. This is one version.</comment>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
There once was a warrior
Fresh from the field
Kneeling before his king he came
When he had risen, he was a knight
and unto his king, this oath he gave.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
I was born on the list field, I was raised in the war
And this day you did make me your knight
though some day my sword may grow rusty and old
I must live by my oath until I die
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
Great grew the knight, and his fame he did win
And never before a foe would yield
great were the numbers, he ne'er called defeat
and he sang this song behind his shield.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c2">
      <lines>
I was born on the list field, I was raised in the war
And one day my king made me a knight
Though some day my sword may grow rusty and old
I must live by my oath until I die.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Old grew the knight and retired to his farm
Said the king &quot;You'll ne'er be called again.&quot;
This knight he knew honor and duty knew well
And unto his king this oath he gave.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c3">
      <lines>
I was born on the list field, I was raised in the war
And one day you did make me a knight
Though some day my sword may grow rusty and old
I must live by my oath until I die.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
War tore the country and the king was in flight
His knights, they could not win the day
Onto the field rode that old ag-ed knight
and some swear they heard him say.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c4">
      <lines>
You were born on the list field, You were raised in the war
And one day they did make you all knights
Though some day your sword may grow rusty and old
You must live by my oaths until I die.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
The king's men they rallied, and they slew all their foes
<comment>slowly</comment>
They began to count their hurt and dead.
They found that ag-ed knight ringed round by slain foes
And unto his king this oath he gave.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c5">
      <lines>
I was born on the list field, I was raised in the war
And one day you did make me a knight
Though seems my sword has grown rusty and old
I have lived by my oath, now I die.
<comment>return to normal speed</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
Stands now the heir to that old aged knight
and to all the legacy he bore
with this sword of my own I know my duty well
And I have my own oath I swore
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c6">
      <lines>
I was born on the list field, I was raised in the war
And it matters not if I'm a knight
Though you see my sword's not yet rusty or old
I must live by my oath 'till I die.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
