<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Crusader's Song</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Conn~MacNeill</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>c1 v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 c2</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
I'm for the Holy Land sailing
To win back Jerusalem's walls
I'm for the Holy Land sailing.
And I'll win a fortune or a martyr I'll fall.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
As my ship sails out I watch the far coastline.
For leaving of kinsmen my heart is full pain.
And I've traded all for this cross on my shoulder
No land for a third son, so I'm away.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
As I look around me at the men on the benches
Their eyes are like mine, so I know their heart's pain.
I sing them a song of bravery in battle
And now their eyes shine like their keen polished blades.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
I followed King Richard to Sicily island.
Johanna's dowry 'gainst Tancred prevailed.
Now a fortune in silver and a new wife hath Richard
And I've a swift horse and a fine coat of mail.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
At landfall in Cypress they refused Berengaria.
Richard in anger has answered in steel.
Now the crown of Cypress he's added to England's
And I've added Knighthood's gold spurs to my heels.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
I followed the banner to battle at Acre.
And held it aloft when its bearer was slain.
Now we've given Richard a tower of the city.
He's given me rank and a full Captain's pay.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
At Arsouf on the coastline we met with the Paynim.
We won the battle though many men fell.
One was a Baron with lands that need tending
Now they are mine and I'll tend them well.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
Now I sit in court over Christian and Moslem
And I've a strong keep and soldiers ten score.
King Richard's army has sailed back to England
I bid them farewell, for I'll see them nay more.
<comment>Spoken: You see...</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c2">
      <lines>
I'm in the Holy Land staying.
To guard my own castle walls.
I'm in the Holy Land staying.
Now I've won my fortune, so farewell to all!
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
