<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Dark Eyed Sailor</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Traditional</author>
    </authors>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
'Twas of a maid both young and fair,
Whilst walking out for to take the air.
She met a sailor all on her way,
And I paid attention, and I paid attention,
To hear what they might say.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
He says, "Fair maid, why roam alone?
For the day's far spent, and the night's coming on."
While crystal tears from her eyes did flow:
"It's my dark-eyed sailor, oh, my dark eyed sailor,
That proved my overthrow."
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
"'Tis three long years since he left this land.
A new gold ring he took off his hand.
He broke this token, gave half to me,
While the other half's lying, the other half's lying
At the bottom of the sea."
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
"Oh,"he says, "Fair maid, drive him off your mind,
For as good a sailor as him you'll find!
Love turns aside, and cold does grow
Like a winter's morning, like a winter's morning,
When the hills are cover'd with snow."
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
"His coal-black eyes and curly hair,
His flatt'ring tongue did my heart ensnare.
Genteel he was, no rake lie you,
To advise a maiden, to advise a maiden
To slight the jacket blue!'
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
"A tarry sailor I'll ne'er disdain,
Always true till he comes again.
So drink his health; here's a piece of coin.
But my dark eyed sailor, but my dark eyed sailor
Still claims this heart of mine."
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
When William did the ring unfold
She seem'd distracted midst joy and woe.
"You're welcome, William; I have lands and gold
For my dark eyed sailor, for my dark eyed sailor,
So manly, true and bold!"
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>
Down in a cottage by a riverside,
In peace and harmony they now reside.
So, girls, prove true whilst your lover's away.
Oft a cloudy morning, oft a cloudy morning
Brings forth a pleasant day.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
