<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Devil and the Farmers Wife</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12 v13</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
There was an old farmer and he lived on a hill;
If he ain't moved away, he's a livin' there still.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
Sing hi diddle I diddle I fye,
Diddle I diddle I day.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
The devil he came to the farmer one day,
Says, &quot;One of your family I'm takin' away.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
&quot;O, please don't take my eldest son,
There's work on the farm that's got to be done.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
&quot;Take my wife with the joy of my heart,
And I hope by golly that you never part.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
The Devil put the old woman into a sack,
And down the road went clickety clack.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
And when they got to the fork of the road,
He says, &quot;Old woman, you're a hell of a load.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
And when they got to the gates of Hell,
He said, &quot;Stoke up the fire, boys, we'll roast her well.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>
Then up stepp'd a devil with ball and chain;
She upped with her foot and kicked out his brain.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>
Then nine little devils went running up the wall,
Crying, &quot;Take her back, Daddy, she'll murder us all.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>
Well, the old man was peekin' through a crack,
When he seen the old Devil come a bringing' her back.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>
&quot;Here's your wife both sound and well,
If she'd stayed any longer she'd a torn up Hell.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>
&quot;I've been a devil most all of my life,
But I never knew what Hell was 'till I met with your wife.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>
This proves that the women are better than the men,
They can all go to Hell and come back again.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
