<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Do Virgins Taste Better?</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>R.~Farran </author>
    </authors>
    <keywords>
      <keyword>An Old Cliche Revisited</keyword>
    </keywords>
    <tune>The Irish Washerwoman</tune>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 c1 v3 v4 c1 v5</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
A dragon has come to our village today.
We've asked him to leave, but he won't go away.
Now he's talked to our king and they worked out a deal.
No homes will he burn and no crops will he steal.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
Now there is but one catch, we dislike it a bunch.
Twice a year he invites him a virgin to lunch.
Well, we've no other choice, so the deal we'll respect.
But we can't help but wonder and pause to reflect.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
Do virgins taste better than those who are not?
Are they salty, or sweeter, more juicy or what?
Do you savor them slowly or gulp them down on the spot?
Do virgins taste better than those who are not?
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Now we'd like to be rid you, and many have tried.
But no one can get through your thick scaly hide.
We hope that some day, some brave knight will come by.
'Cause we can't wait around 'til you're too fat to fly.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
Now you have such good taste in your women for sure,
They always are pretty, they always are pure.
Bid your notion of dining, it makes us all flinch,
For your favorite entrée is barbecued wench.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
Now we've found a solution, it works out so neat,
If you insist on nothing but virgins to eat.
No more will our number ever grow small,
Well simply make sure there's no virgins at all!
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
