<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Dream Warrior</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Rathflaed~DuNoir</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 c1 v3 v4 c1 v5 v6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
He gets up every morning and he goes to work each day,
He sees his friends and family, he works and then he plays,
But they never get to see the one he keeps so deep inside,
The one he really wants to be he feels that he must hide.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
He works in an assembly line in a downtown factory,
He does his job the best he can, but it's not where he wants to be,
Outside the gate, his charger waits! but only he can see,
So it's back to the grind for another day, oh when will he be free?
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
He's a dream warrior, he rides across the lands.
He's a dream warrior, there's magic in his hands,
And yet he fears the people near, he's afraid that they won't see
So he hides away within himself, with his pride, and his chivalry
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Now the day is done and it's home from work, to see his kids and wife.
To him she is a princess, she's led a sheltered life.
In a tower of blue he pays his dues, his lady captured waits,
Then he turns into his driveway past the mailbox and the gate.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
He tells his kids a bedtime tale, his daughter and his son,
Of wizards and knights, and mighty kings, and battles fought and won,
Then it's off to sleep, and he dreams so deep, as in his bed he lays,
So he fights tonight! because he knows that tomorrow, is a busy day.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
His honor still comes first to him but it gets harder every day,
To see the ones around him breaking promises they've made.
So he keeps his own, and like a stone, in him they'll never know,
The way he really lives his life, the way he'll never show.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
Because he'll never quit the cause, he'll never give up his dreams,
And he'll live his life all by himself, or so to him it seems,
Because they might think he's crazy and they might think it's just a whim,
So he wonders if he'll ever meet someone who's just like him.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
