<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Eileen Aroon </title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Irish Traditional</author>
    </authors>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
When, like the dawning day, Eileen Aroon
Love sends his early ray, Eileen Aroon
What makes his dawning glow
Only the constant know, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
When, like the early rose, Eileen Aroon
Beauty in childhood blows, Eileen Aroon
When like a diadem buds blush around the stem
Which is the fairest gem Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
I know a valley fair, Eileen Aroon
I know a cottage there, Eileen Aroon
Far in the valley shade I know a tender maid
Flow'r of the hazel glade, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
Who in the song so sweet, Eileen Aroon
Who in the dance so fleet, Eileen Aroon
Dear are her charms to me, dearer her laughter free
Dearest her constancy, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
Is it the laughing eye, Eileen Aroon
Is it the timid sigh, Eileen Aroon
Is it the tender tone, soft as the stringed harps note
Oh, it is truth alone, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
When like the rising day, Eileen Aroon
Love sends her early ray, Eileen Aroon
What makes her dawning gleam, changeless through joy or woe
Only the constant know, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
Were she no longer true, Eileen Aroon
What would her lover do, Eileen Aroon
Fly with a broken chain, far o'er the sounding main
Never to love again, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>
Youth will in time decay, Eileen Aroon
Beauty must fade away, Eileen Aroon
Castles are sacked in war, chieftains are scattered far
Truth is a fixed star, Eileen Aroon.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
