<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Finnegan's Wake</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Traditional</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
Tim Finnegan lived on Walker Street
A gentleman, Irish, mighty odd;
He had a brogue both rich and sweet
And to rise in the world he carried a hod.
Now Tim had a sort of the tipplin' way
With a love of the whiskey he was born
And to help him on with his work each day
He'd a &quot;drop of the cray-thur&quot; every morn.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
Whack fol the darn O, dance to your partner
Whirl the floor, your trotters shake;
Wasn't it the truth I told you
Lots of fun at Finnegan's wake!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
One mornin' Tim was feelin' full
His head was heavy which made him shake;
He fell from the ladder and broke his skull
And they carried him home his corpse to wake.
They rolled him up in a nice clean sheet
And laid him out upon the bed,
With a gallon of whiskey at his feet
And a barrel of porter at his head.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
His friends assembled at the wake
And Mrs. Finnegan called for lunch,
First they brought in tea and cake
Then pipes, tobacco and whiskey punch.
Biddy O'Brien began to bawl
&quot;Such a nice clean corpse, did you ever see?
&quot;Aye Tim, mavourneen, why did you die?&quot;
&quot;Arragh, hold your gob&quot; said Paddy McGee!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
Then Maggie O'Connor took up the job
&quot;O Biddy,&quot; says she, &quot;You're wrong, I'm sure&quot;
Biddy she gave her a belt in the gob
And left her sprawlin' on the floor.
And then the war did soon engage
'Twas woman to woman and man to man,
Shillelagh law was all the rage
And a row and eruption soon began.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
Then Mickey Maloney ducked his head
When a noggin of whiskey flew at him,
It missed, and fallin' on the bed
The liquor scattered over Tim!
The corpse revives! See how he raises!
Timothy rising from the bed,
ays, &quot;Whirl your whiskey around like blazes
Thanum an Dhul! Did you think I'm dead?&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
