<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Hotspur</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Andrew of Wolvenwood</author>
    </authors>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
Squire, bring my armor, my sword and my destrier.
I've raised an army to break Henry's power.
South from the Humber, we've marched to the Severn,
With Douglas of Scotland, to join with Glendower.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
So ready your weapons, and don warlike harness,
The King rides to greet us at Shrewsbury town.
He'll pay what he owes me, or fight on the morrow.
The Blue Lion of Percy will bloody the ground.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Hal Prince of Wales has brought forth an army,
To halt us he's planning, he bars naught to me.
Yon rides his father, a king made by Percy,
His host in the thousands, a hard fight will be.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
So let loose your clothyards my stout Cheshire yeoman,
The hiss of your bowstrings, tis soft as a sigh.
Now King's knights you've halted, so up roar the horsemen,
We charge for the center, brave Douglas and I.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
Lay low a sergeant, and then slay his master,
Rend through the armor, and hew clear a way.
There by the banner, the King rides before me,
I swear by my honor, tis his final day.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
But Prince Hal has broken my right wing of battle,
And he's for his father, a whirlin' around.
Now one of his yeomen has sent me an arrow,
The Blue Lion of Percy is pulled to the ground.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
Squire bring my armor, my sword and destrier.
I'll live forever to spite Bolingbroke!
Know then of Hotspur who died by the Severn,
And list what was heard when Lord Percy spoke:
<comment>softly</comment>
      </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>
Ready your weapons, and don warlike harness,
The King rides to greet us at Shrewsbury town.
He'll pay what he owes me, or fight on the morrow,
The Blue Lion of Percy will bloody the ground.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
