<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Itsy Bitsy Teenie Weenie Little Rabbit Fur Bikini</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>W.J.~Bethancourt~III</author>
    </authors>
    <tune>Itsy Bitsy Teenie Weenie Yellow Polka Dot Bikini</tune>
    <copyright>Public domain</copyright>
    <keywords>
      <keyword>Rabbit Fur Bikini</keyword>
    </keywords>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 c2 v3 c3 v4 c4</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
She was afraid to come out to the Tourney
She was worried that &quot;something might show..&quot;
She was afraid to come out to the Tourney
And the poor thing did NOT want to go...
<comment>2 - 3 - 4, tell the people what she wore!</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
It was an itsy bitsy teeny weenie little rabbit fur bikini
That she wore, for the first time, that day.
An itsy bitsy teenie weenie little rabbit fur bikini
And in her apartment she wanted to stay!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
One day in the Kingdom of the Middle
It happened at a Tourney one day:
The Mongols invaded the Middle
But the Middle did not want to play...
<comment>eins - zwei - drei, but the Dark Horde wouldn't die!</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c2">
      <lines>
It was an itsy bitsy tiny teenie Nauseating Mongol weenie
That they saw, for the first time, that day.
An itsy bitsy tiny teenie Nauseating Mongol weenie
And the Mongols did NOT go away!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Now the Heralds made up a new Rulebook
And to read it is some kind of gas!
It's a bureaucrat's dream, this new Rulebook
Now NOBODY'S blazon can pass!
<comment>Win - Place - Show, tell the Heralds where to go!</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c3">
      <lines>
I want an itsy bitsy teenie weenie little rabbit fur bikini
On my shield, as my blazon, today!
An itsy bitsy teenie weenie little rabbit fur bikini
But &quot;that's offensive&quot; the Heralds all say!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
I sat down at the Revel last evening
To a feast of green meat, and Rat Pie...
It was cold, and disgusting, and greasy
And I just want to upchuck and die!
<comment>6 - 7 - 8, tell them what was on your plate!</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c4">
      <lines>
It was an itsy bitsy teenie weenie little rabbit fur bikini
With a side dish of cold cabbage pie!
An itsy bitsy teenie weenie little rabbit fur bikini
With the fur on, and NOTHING inside!
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
