<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Kelly, the Boy from Killanne</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Traditional</author>
    </authors>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
What's the news? What's the news? O my bold Shelmalier,
With your long-barrelled gun, from the sea?
A wind from the south brings a messenger dear
With a hymn of the dawn for the free?
"Goodly news, goodly news, do I bring, youth of Forth,
Goodly news do I bring, Bargy man!
For the boys march at dawn from the south to the north
Led by Kelly, the boy from Killanne!"
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
Tell me who is the giant with the gold curling hair,
He who rides at the head of your van
Seven feet is his height, with some inches to spare
And he looks like a king in command!
"Oh, me boys, that's the pride of the bold Shelmaliers,
"Mongst our greatest of heroes, a man!
Fling your beavers aloft and your three ringin' cheers
John Kelly, the boy from Killanne!"
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Enniscorthy's in flames, and old Wexford is won,
And the Barrow tomorrow we cross.
On a hill o'er the town we have planted a gun
That will batter the gateways to Ross!
All the Forth men and Bargy men march over the heath
Brave Harvey to lead on the van;
But the foremost of all in that grim gap of death
Will be Kelly, the boy from Killanne!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
Now the bold sun of freedom grew darkened at Ross
And it set by the Slaney's red waves;
And poor Wexford, stripped naked, hung high on a cross
With her heart pierced by traitors and slaves!
Glory O! Glory O! to her brave sons who died
For the cause of long-down-trodden man!
Glory O! to mount Leinster's own darling and pride:
John Kelly, the boy from Killanne!
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
