<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Leave Her Johnny</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>A. Author</author>
      <author>B. Authour</author>
    </authors>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12 v13 v14 v15</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
O the times are hard and the wages low,
Leave her, Johnny, leave her!
I think it's time for us to go!
An' it's time for us to leave her!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
Leave her, Johnny, leave her!
Oh, leave her, Johnny, leave her!
For the voyage is done an' the winds don't blow,
An' it's time for us to leave her!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
O I thought I heard the old man say,
Tomorrow ye will get your pay!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
It's Liverpool Pat with his tarpaulin hat,
It's Yankee John the packet rat.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
It's rotten beef an' weev'ly bread,
It's pump or drown the old man said.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
The wind was foul an' the sea ran high,
She shipped it green an' none went by.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
We'd be better off in a nice clean gaol,
With all night in an' plenty o' ale!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
The mate was a bucko an' the old man a Turk,
The bosun was a beggar with the middle name o' work!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>
It's growl yer may an' go yer must,
It matters not whether yer last or first!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>
The cook's a drunk, he likes to booze,
'tween him an' the mate there's little to choose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>
I hate to sail on this rotten tub,
No grog allowed and rotten grub!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>
The ship won't steer, or stay, or wear,
An' so us shellbacks learnt to swear.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>
No Liverpool bread, nor rotten crackerhash,
No dandyfunk, nor cold an' sloppy hash.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>
The old man shouts, the pumps stand by,
Oh, we can never suck her dry.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>
Now I thought I hear the old man say,
Just one more pull an' then belay.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v15">
      <lines>
We swear by rote for want o' more,
But now we're through so we'll go on shore.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
