<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Long Distance Squire</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Galen~of~Bristol</author>
      <author>Genvieve~McCullum~du~Caen</author>
    </authors>
    <tune>Cats in the Cradle</tune>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
Squired a lad just the other day
Gave him his belt in the usual way
But there were wars to fight, and men to slay
He made his sword while I was away
And he was fighting 'fore I knew it, and as he grew
He'd say &quot;I'm going to be like you, Sir
You know I'm going to be like you&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
And the cats in the cradle, and the silver spoon
Little Squire boy, and the Man in the Moon
When you coming home, Sir? I don't know when
But we'll get together then, Squire
You know we'll have a good fight then
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
He became a lord just the other day
He said &quot;Thanks for the shield, Sir, come on, let's play
Can you teach me to kill?&quot; I said &quot;Not today
I got a lot to do.&quot; He said &quot;That's okay&quot;
And he walked away, but his smile never dimmed
He said &quot;I'm going to be like him, yeah
You know I'm going to be like him&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
He came from Pennsic just the other day
So much like a Knight I just had to say
&quot;Squire I'm proud of you, can you fight for a while?&quot;
He shook his head and he said with a smile
&quot;What I'd really like, Sir, is to borrow your tent please
See you later, will you leave us in peace?&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
He's long been a knight, he's traveled far away
I saw him here just the other day
&quot;I'd like to learn that snap blow, if you don't mind?&quot;
He said &quot;I'd teach you, Sir, if I could find the time
But see the new Crown's a hassle, and the squires are new
But it's been nice sparring with you&quot;
And as the King walked away, it occurred to me
He'd grown up just like me. My Squire was just like me
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
