<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Lord Randal</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
O where have you been, Lord Randal, my son?
O where have you been, my bonny young man?
I've been with my sweetheart, mother make my bed soon
For I'm sick to the heart and I fain would lie down.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
And what did she give you, Lord Randal, my son?
And what did she give you, my bonny young man?
Eels boiled in brew, mother make my bed soon
For I'm sick to the heart and I fain would lie down.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
What's become of your bloodhounds, Lord Randal, my son?
What's become of your bloodhounds, my bonny young man?
O they swelled and died, mother make my bed soon
For I'm sick to the heart and I fain would lie down.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
O I fear you are poisoned, Lord Randal, my son,
O I fear you are poisoned, my bonny young man.
O yes, I am poisoned, mother make my bed soon
For I'm sick to the heart and I fain would lie down.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
What will you leave your brother, Lord Randal, my son?
What will you leave your brother, my bonny young man?
My horse and the saddle, mother make my bed soon
For I'm sick to the heart and I fain would lie down.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
What will you leave your sister, Lord Randal, my son?
What will you leave your sister, my bonny young man?
My gold box and rings, mother make my bed soon
For I'm sick to the heart and I fain would lie down.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
What will you leave your true love, Lord Randal, my son?
What will you leave your true love, my bonny young man?
The tow and the halter to hang on yon tree,
And let her hang there for the poisoning of me.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
