<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Molecatcher</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Traditional</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <comment>Collected by Bob Copper in about 1954 from Jim Barrett, at the Fox in North Waltham, Hants</comment>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
At Manchester City the sign of the Plough,
There lives an old molecatcher, I can't tell you how.
He goes a-molecatching from morning till night
While the jolly young farmer goes playing with his wife.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
Singing law-til-i-day, law-tili-little-i, law-til-i-day.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
The molecatcher jealous of the very same thing,
So he hides in the bake-house and saw him come in,
And when that young farmer got over the stile
It caused the molecatcher to laugh and to smile.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
He knocked at the door and thus he did say,
Pray, where is your husband, good woman, I say.
He's gone a-molecatching, you need not fear,
But little did she think the molecatcher was near.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
She went upstairs - he followed the sign,
And the molecatcher followed them closely behind,
And when that young farmer was in the midst of his sport
The molecatcher grabbed him quite fast by his coat.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
He clapped his hands and laughed at the sight,
Saying, &quot;This is the finest mole I've catched in me life.
I'll make you pay well for ploughing my ground
And the money it shall be no less than ten pound.&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
&quot;Very well&quot;, said the farmer, &quot;the money I don't mind,
For it only costs me about twopence a time.&quot;
So come all you young farmer chaps, mind what you're at
And never get caught in a molecatcher's trap.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
