<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Moose Song</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Thomas~Payton</author>
      <author>Anonymous</author>
    </authors>
    <tune>Betsy From Pike</tune>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12 v13 v14</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
When I was a young girl I used to like boys,
I fondled their tights and played with their toys,
But me boy-friend ran off with a salesman named Bruce,
You'd never get treatment like that from a Moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
So it's Moose, Moose, I like a Moose,
I've never had anything quite like a Moose,
I've had many lovers, my life has been loose,
But I've never had anything quite like a Moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
Now when I'm in need of a very good lay,
I go to me stables and gets me some hay,
I opens me window and spreads it around,
'Cause Moose always comes when there's hay on the ground!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
Now I've made it with all kinds of beasties with hair,
I'd make it with snakes if their fangs were not there,
I've made it with walrus, two ducks and a goose,
But I've never had anything quite like a Moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
Now gorillas are fine for a Saturday night,
And lions and tigers, they puts up a fight,
But it just ain't the same when you slams your caboose
As the feeling you gets when you humps with a Moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
I've tried many beasties on land or on sea
I've even tried hump-backs that humped back on me!
Sharks are quite good, though they're hard to pull loose
But on dry land there is nothing quite like a moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
Woodchucks are all right except that they bite
And foxes and rabbits won't last thru the night!
Cows would be fun, but they're hard to seduce
But you never need worry should you find a moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>
Step in my study, and trophies you'll find
A black striped tiger and scruffy maned lion
You'll know the elephant by his ivory tooth
And the one that's a-winking, you know is the moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>
The lion succumbed to a thirty-ought-six
Machine guns and tigers I've proved do not mix
The elephant fell by a bomb with a fuse
But I won't tell a soul how I did in the moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>
I've found many women attracted to me
A few of them have had me over for tea
Some say that they love me when they're feeling loose
But I'd trade the world's women for one lovely moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>
The good Lord made Adam, and then He made Eve
Said He: &quot;If you sin now, I'll ask you to leave!&quot;
They left not because of Eve's forbidden fruit
But 'cause Adam decided the moose there were cute!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>
The English are said to like boars who've had corn
The Celtics just dream of the young Unicorn
The Germans, it's said, just need leather and rope
But give me a moose and I'll no longer mope!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>
Now I've broken the laws in this god-awful state
They've put me in prison and locked up the gate
They say that tomorrow I'll swing from a noose
But my last night I'll spend with a good sexy moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>
Next morning the Governor's word reached my ears
&quot;We've commuted your sentence to ninety-nine years!&quot;
&quot;You won't get parole; not a five minute's truce,
And your friend goes to Sing-Sing, he's so big-a-moose!&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>
(slowly) Now that I'm old and advanced in me years,
I'll look back on me life, and I'll shed me no tears,
As I sit in me chair with me glass of Mateuse,
And play hide the salami with Marvin the Moose!
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
