<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Sleeping Scotsman</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
A Scotsman clad in kilt left a bar one evening fair
And one could tell by how he walked he'd drunk more than his share
He stumbled on until he could no longer keep his feet
Then staggered off into the grass to sleep, beside the street
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
A ring-di-diddle-e-di do, a-ring-di-diddle-i-day
He staggered off into the grass to sleep beside the street.
<comment>following choruses as above, repeating last line of verse</comment>
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
A pair of young and lovely girls just happened to come by
And one said to the other, with a twinkle in her eye:
&quot;You see yon sleeping Scotsman, so strong and handsome built;
I wonder if it's true what they don't wear beneath their kilt?&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
They crept upon the sleeping Scotsman, quiet as could be,
And lifted up his kilt above the waist, so they could see.
And there, behold, for them to view, beneath his Scottish skirt
'Twas nothing but what God has graced him with upon his birth!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
They marveled for a moment, then one said: &quot;We'd best be gone.
But let's leave a present for our friend before we move along!&quot;
So as a gift, they left a blue silk ribbon, tied into a bow,
Around the Bonnie Star the Scottish kilt did lift and show!
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
The Scotsman woke to Nature's Call, and stumbled towards a tree
Behind the bush, he lifts his kilt, and gawks at what he sees!
Then, in a startled voice he says to what's before his eyes:
&quot;I ken na' whaur y'been, m'lad, but I see y'won First Prize!&quot;
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
