<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Song of the Nightwatch</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Conn~MacNeill</author>
    </authors>
    <keywords>
      <keyword>We Of The Third Estate</keyword>
    </keywords>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
&quot;Three estates,&quot; say the priests, &quot;ordained by God.
The first one is endlessly tilling the sod
The second entreats for our souls to the Lord
And the third estate lives by the sword&quot;
And the third estate dies by the sword
And we are the makers of war.
We are the slayers of thousands.
We shall be wounded for those who lie safe.
We of the third estate.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
The merchants live richly, all haughty and vain.
They bargain for profit, our office disdain.
They greed for their safety as great as for gold.
No they would not live by the sword
And they would not die by the sword
Yet  blows are the coins of war
And we've come to bargain sternly
We shall be wounded for those who ply trade.
We of the third estate.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
The villein he laboreth all day in the sun,
Yet safely he sleeps when his day's work is done.
He would not hazard his flesh to be torn
No he would not live by the sword
And he would not die by the sword.
Yet swords are the scythes of war
And we've come to reap a grim harvest
We shall be wounded for reapers of grain.
We of the third estate.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
The bishops and priests warn us well of sin's perils;
Of tournaments, feasting, temptations, and devils.
They save their whole skins as well as their souls
No they would not live by the sword
And they would not die by the sword
Yet screams are the prayers of war
High mass shall be sung by our foemen
We shall be wounded for those who pray.
We of the third estate.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
Tonight I keep watch while the rain chills my bones.
I know weariness, hunger, am far from my home.
But there is no company I could love more
Than those men who would live by the sword
And those men who would die by the sword
For the wine of true living is war
From its cup my fellows drink deeply
We shall give battle like true men this day.
We of the Third Estate.
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
