<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.9">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Whiskey in the Jar</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Traditional</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 c1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>
As I was going over the far famed Kerry mountains
I met with Captain Farrell and his money he was counting.
I first produced my pistol, and then produced my rapier.
Said stand and deliver, for I am a bold deceiver,
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>
musha ring dumma do damma da
whack for the daddy 'ol
whack for the daddy 'ol
there's whiskey in the jar
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>
I counted out his money, and it made a pretty penny.
I put it in my pocket and I took it home to Jenny.
She said and she swore, that she never would deceive me,
but the devil take that woman, for she never could be easy
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>
I went into my chamber, all for to take a slumber,
I dreamt of gold and jewels and for sure it was no wonder.
But Jenny took my charges and she filled them up with water,
Then sent for Captain Farrel to be ready for the slaughter.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>
It was early in the morning, as I rose up for travel,
The guards were all around me and likewise Captain Farrel.
I first produced my pistol, for she stole away my rapier,
But I couldn't shoot the water so a prisoner I was taken.
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>
If anyone can aid me, it's my brother in the army,
If I can find his station down in Cork or in Killarney.
And if he'll come and save me, we'll go roving near Kilkenny,
And I swear he'll treat me better than me darling sporting Jenny
</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>
Now some men take delight in the drinking and the roving,
But others take delight in the gambling and the smoking.
But I take delight in the juice of the barley,
And courting pretty fair maids in the morning bright and early
</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
